# Wenhan Miaoui/ux Designer

Langley, BC. 778-551-9133 Wenhanm@sfu.ca



#### **DESIGN EXPERIENCE**

### **Educational Designer (CO-OP)** — City of Surrey, Surrey, BC.

September 2022 - April 2023

Worked closely with the client-Manager of Engineering, to design nine independent training modules for Engineering Department staff. Provided the client with multiple design options, carried out the design using Articulate Storyline 360 to create interactive modules, then led multiple stages of feedback collecting and user testing to ensure the modules are user-friendly and engaging.

## **Logo Designer, Branding Assistance** — Supreme Freeze Dry Ltd, Coquitlam, BC.

May 2020 - August 2020

Worked closely with the owner of the company to redesign their previous logo. Came up with different prototypes, discussed them with the client and finalized the end product together. Assisted the owner with their overall branding to achieve a coherent brand image and identity, ranging from photographing products to discussing layout options with the website development team.

#### **ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE**

# **Game Programming/ Design** — IAT 167, Digital Games Programming

January 2022 - April 2022

Fully designed and programmed a multilevel platform shooting game using the coding platform Processing. Integrated game sounds and achieved animation effects by using stop-motion animation and looping the individual digitally drawn images in arrays.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Figma
- ProtoPie
- Processing
- Visual Design
- User Research
- Branding

#### **AWARDS**

- · 3rd place in the 4th World Cup Painting Competition- Final Round
- · 2nd place in the 4th World Cup Painting Competition-Preliminary Round
- · 2nd place in The 11th International Angel Cup Painting Competition
- World Youth
   Leadership Award

### **App Design, Target Market Research** — BUS 238,

Entrepreneurship and Innovation

October 2020 - December 2020

Completed 22 interviews and examined the findings to identify the core problem. Worked together with team members to create a prototype for an app aimed at encouraging authentic connections among single millennials, based on feedback from interviewees who indicated this was missing in popular dating apps. Developed a business model, customer persona, and designed the app in a team environment with features that address the identified issue.

# PERSONAL OUALITIES

- · Growth mindset
- · Team player
- · Optimistic
- Introspective

### **OTHER EXPERIENCE**

**Educator** — Lululemon, Moorabbin, Melbourne.

August 2023- January 2024

Demonstrate in-depth knowledge of Lululemon's product offerings, including fabrics, fits, and features, to effectively assist customers in making informed purchasing decisions. Participate in ongoing personal skills training and team development opportunities.

### LANGUAGES

Able to speak both English and Mandarin fluently, currently learning Italian.

# Management Assistant/ Sales Development Representative — Supreme Freeze Dry Ltd, Coquitlam, BC.

February 2017 - June 2022

Assists management with customer relationships, product development and general implementation. Set up and attend meetings with potential/existing clients and respond to public inquiries through company email.

#### **EDUCATION**

Simon Fraser
University - Surrey,
BC — BSc in
Interactive Arts and
Technology
September 2020 present.

Monash University Australia — Study Abroad Term July 2023 - January 2024.

### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

**Secretary,** SFU- Math Student Union(MSU) — Surrey, BC

January 2021 - June 2021

Took club attendance, generated session summaries for every meeting, as well as helped brainstorm for club activities, planned for events, conduct surveys, brainstorm and group problem-solving.